Guide to the Department of Zoology records, 1873-1965.
Department of Zoology records
- Series II. Correspondence
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1954-1955
    - Summer Session, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - T, correspondents by last name, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Technicon Company, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - University Library, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - V, W, correspondents by last name, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - Veterinary College, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - Ward's Natural Science Establishment, Inc., 11955 (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - Will Corporation, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - Wright, T. P., 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1955-1956
    - A, correspondents by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Applications, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Applications for Graduate School, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Assistantship and Admissions, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Assistantship, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Assistantship cont., 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - B, correspondents by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - C, correspondents by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - D, correspondents by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Dean, Office of the, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Department Chemical Order, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Department Graduate Students, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Department Letters of Recommendation, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Department Staff Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Directory of Staff, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - E, correspondents by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - G, correspondents by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Graduate School, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - J, correspondents by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - K, correspondents by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - L, correspondents by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - McKeegan, Paul L., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Microscope Case, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Ornithology, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - P, correspondents by last name, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Personnel Director, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Phi Kappa Phi, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Positions at other institutions, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - President, Office of the, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Provost, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Public Information, Office of, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Purchasing Department, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - R, correspondence by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Research, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Rural Education Department, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Summer Session, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - T, correspondents by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Traffic Control, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - U, correspondents by last name, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - University Faculty, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - University Library, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - V, correspondents by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Veterinary College, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - W, correspondents by last name, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Wright, T. P., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1956-1957
    - A, correspondents by last name, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Anderson, John M., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Assistantship Applications, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Applications for Department Positions, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - B, correspondents by last name, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 57)
      Includes blueprints of Stimson Hall
    - Buildings and Grounds - Job Orders, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - C, correspondents by last name, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Collection of Regional History, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Controller, Office of the, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - College Faculty Self-Evaluation, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - D, correspondents by last name, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Department Courses and Students, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Department Chemical Order, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Department Staff Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Directory of Staff, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Department Inventory, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Department Letters of Recommendation, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Department Staff Meetings, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Department Research Grant, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Education, School of, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - F, correspondents by last name, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - G, correspondents by last name, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 74)
      Contains a piece of coral attached to a letter
    - Graduate School, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Graduate School Applications, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Graduate School Recommendations, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Graduate School Applications, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Graduate School Applications, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Hastie, John W., 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Humphrey, Rufus R., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - I, correspondents by last name, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Ithaca Staff Purchases, Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - K, correspondents by last name, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - L, correspondents by last name, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Library, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - National Science Foundation, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - National Science Foundation cont., 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - P, correspondence by last name, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Payroll Office, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Personnel Office, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Poritsky, Raphael, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Positions at other institutions, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - President, Office of the, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Public Information Department, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Purchasing Department, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - R, correspondents by last name, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Research Club, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Safety Division, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - Schneiderman, Howard A., 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - Summer Session, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - University Faculty Meetings, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - V, correspondents by last name, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - W, correspondents by last name, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - Will Corporation, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - Wright, T. P., 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1957-1958
    - A, B, correspondents by last name, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Buildings and Properties, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Includes blueprints for Stimson Hall
    - C, correspondents by last name, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Cheney, Alexander J., 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Controller's Office, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - D, correspondents by last name, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Dean, Office of the, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Department Staff Applications, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Department of Purchasing, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Department Annual Inventory, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Department Letters of Recommendation, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Department Staff Correspondence, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - E, correspondents by last name, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - G, correspondents by last name, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Graduate School, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Graduate School Applications, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Hastie, John W., 1958 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Ithaca Staff Purchases, Inc., 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - L, correspondents by last name, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - National Science Foundation, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - New York Telephone Company, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Natural Sciences Academy, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Personnel Director, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Peterson, A. H., 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Positions at other institutions, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Public Information, Office of, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Purchasing Department, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - R, correspondents by last name, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Schering Corporation, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Summer Session, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - T, correspondents by last name, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Terwillegar, R. E., 1958 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Traffic Control, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - W, correspondence by last name, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Wirth, Elizabeth Bailly, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Wright, T. P., 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence with Howard B. Adelmann 1958-1959
    - A, correspondence by last name, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Academic Work and Interest, Student Committee on, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Applications for Department Positions, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - B, correspondents by last name, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Budget, Office of the Director of the, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Buildings and Properties, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - C, correspondents by last name, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Controller, Office of the, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Department Information, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Department of Purchasing, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Department Staff Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - E, correspondents by last name, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - G, correspondence by last name, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Graduate School Students, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Graduate School, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Holz, George G., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - K, L, correspondents by last name, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Leonard, Samuel L., 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - O, correspondents by last name, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - P, correspondents by last name, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Personnel Director, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Positions at other institutions, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Pre-Medical Advisers, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - President, Office of the, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Provost, Office of the, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Purchasing Department, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - R, correspondents by last name, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Recommendation, Letters of, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Research Coordinator, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Safety Division, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Seaman, Arlene, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Summer Session, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Station, Field Biological, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Traffic Control Board, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Union, Cornell Federal Credit, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - University Library, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - University Staff Directory, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - University Telephone Manager, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - University Typewriter Division, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Vallentyne, J. R., 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Van der Kloot, William G., 1958 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Veterinary College, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence with William A. Wimsatt 1959-1960
    - A, correspondents by last name, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Air Travel Accidental Death and Dismemberment Policy, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Buildings and Properties, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Controller, Office of the, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Cornell Federal Credit Union, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Chairman of the Subcommittee on Undergraduate Library, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Control, Board on Traffic, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - D, correspondents by last name, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Dean, Office of the, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Day Hall, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Department Position Applications, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Department Letters of Recommendation, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Department Staff Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - E, correspondents by last name, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Ithaca Staff Purchases, Inc., 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Kennedy, W. K., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Leonard, Samuel L., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - National Science Foundation, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Napier, Frank C., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Proposal for Budget, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Payroll, Office of the, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Personnel Department, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Positions at other institutions, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Problems, Committee on Admission, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Provost, Office of the, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Purchasing Department, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Reed, Marilyn, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Safety Division, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Summer Session, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Trevisi, Massimo, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - University Editor's Office - Staff Directory, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - University Brain Collection, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 123)
      Letter concerning the donation of Charles H Herrick's brain to the Wilder Brain Collection
    - Wright, T. P., 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Ziegelmair, Claire A., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Correspondence with William A. Wimsatt 1960-1961
    - Academics, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - B, correspondents by last name, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Buildings and Properties, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Cornell Accidental Injury Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 129)
      Includes report of vampire bat bite
    - Cosmopolitan Magazine, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Communications Division, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Controller, Office of the, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - Cornell Federal Credit Union, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Department Staff Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Department Position Applications, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Directory of Staff, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - E, correspondents by last name, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 137)
      Includes letter from Susan A. Glasgow
    - Export, Shipping, and Forwarding Agents, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Graduate School, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - Hastie, J. W., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - Ithaca Staff Purchases, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Kapp, Walter L., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - Kennedy, W. K., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 143)
    - M, N, P, correspondents by last name, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 144)
    - Nutrition, Graduate School of, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 145)
    - Payroll Office, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 146)
    - Personnel Director, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 147)
    - Policy, Insurance, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 148)
      Includes a letter from J. R. Vallentyne concerning a fire on his property that destroyed research equipment
    - R, correspondents by last name, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 149)
    - Recommendation, Letters of, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 150)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 151)
    - Research Coordinator, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 152)
    - Singer, Marcus, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 153)
    - Summer Session, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 154)
    - Van Cleef Memorial Library, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 155)
    - Ward's Natural Science Establishment, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - Correspondence with William A. Wimsatt 1961-1962
    - Auditor, Office of the, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 157)
    - B, C, correspondents by last name, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 158)
    - Communications Division, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 159)
    - Controller, Office of the, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 160)
    - Coordinator of Research, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 162)
    - Dean, Office of the, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 163)
    - Department Staff Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 164)
    - Directory of Staff, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 165)
    - Department of Zoology in SCIENCE, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 166)
    - Department Letters of Recommendation, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 167)
    - Department Applications, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Eapen, Jacob, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Graduate School, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - H, correspondents by last name, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Ithaca College, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Land, Hugh C., 1962 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Malott, Deane W., 1961 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - McKeegan, Paul, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Payroll Office, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Personnel Director, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Stimson Hall Maintenance - Department of Buildings and Properties, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Safety Department Accidental Injury Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Summer Session, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Traffic Control Board, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - University Graduate Studies, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Vallentyne, John R., 1961 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence with William A. Wimsatt 1962-1963
    - A, correspondents by last name, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Admissions, Office of, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Applications, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Auditor's Office, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Cornell Research, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Cornell Federal Credit Union, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - D, correspondents by last name, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Includes a letter from Pamela Felton and a response by Perry W. Gilbert
    - Dean, Office of the, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Department Position Applications, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - G, correspondents by last name, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Graduate School, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Holz, George G., 1962 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous Requests, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - May, Margaret T., 1962 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - McKeegan, Paul, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Moore, A. C., 1962 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Payroll Division, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Personnel Director, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Rogers, Ann M., 1962 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Request for Issuance of Certificate of Eligibility for Exchange Visitor Status, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Recordak Corporation, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Research Club, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Roberts, E. R., 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Supervisor's Accident Report, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Staff Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Schmidt, Fatanitza, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Summer Employment, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Summer Session, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Traffic Control Board, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - W, correspondents by last name, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Weinhold, Julius, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence with William A. Wimsatt 1963-1964
    - A, correspondents by last name, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Auditor, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Buildings and Properties, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Coffin, Tristram, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Change in extension number, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Contingency Fund for Research, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Controller, Office of the, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Cornell Federal Credit Union, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Coordinator of Research Instruction, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Dahlen, Mary Ellen, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Dean, Office of the, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Department Staff, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Directory of Staff, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Department Position Applications, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - G, correspondents by last name, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Graduate School, 1960-1964 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Internal Revenue Service, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - K, L, correspondents by last name, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - M, correspondents by last name, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - McFarland, William, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - McLean Preserve, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Page, Ernest W., 1963 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Payroll Division, Treasurer's Office, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Personnel Director, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Peebles, Charles R., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Purchasing Department, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Registrar, Office of the, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Roberts, E. R., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - S, correspondents by last name, 1961-1964 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Safety Supervisor, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Summer Session, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Treasurer, Office of the, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - Typewriter Division, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - Use of Space Survey, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - Vajropala, Kloom, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - Warner, Eldon D., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence with LaMont C. Cole 1964-1965
    - Dean, Office of the, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Department Staff, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - Directory of Staff, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - G, correspondents by last name, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - Graduate School, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 94)